<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | Hugo Academic CV Theme</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language>
    <image>
      <url>http://localhost:1313/media/icon_hu_645fa481986063ef.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Multi-Drones Tracking (ongoing, and highly likely that a paper will be published)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/multi-uav-tracking-by-3d-ukf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/multi-uav-tracking-by-3d-ukf/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sept. 2024 - Present&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Advisor:&lt;/strong&gt; Prof. Yanyong Zhang (Computer Science, USTC)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Current project involves creating a 3D-UKF structure and using IMM-UKF to track drones.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;My task is to assist in completing the theoretical derivation and coding for uniform circular motion (CT) and constant acceleration motion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;The project is ongoing, and it is highly likely that a paper will be published.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;video-simulations&#34;&gt;Video Simulations&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;ct-kf-tracking-simulation&#34;&gt;CT-KF Tracking Simulation&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is the simulation video showcasing CT-KF tracking:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;video width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;360&#34; controls&gt;
  &lt;source src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/uploads/CTdemo.mov&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34;&gt;
  Your browser does not support the video tag.
&lt;/video&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&#34;ca-kf-tracking-simulation&#34;&gt;CA-KF Tracking Simulation&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is the simulation video showcasing CA-KF tracking:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;video width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;360&#34; controls&gt;
  &lt;source src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/uploads/CAdemo.mp4&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34;&gt;
  Your browser does not support the video tag.
&lt;/video&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nash Equilibrium Guandan</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/guandan-gaming/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/guandan-gaming/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;May 2024 - Sept. 2024&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Advisor:&lt;/strong&gt; Prof. Kani Chen (Financial Mathematics, HKUST)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Worked under Professor Ka-Ni Chan at the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology to develop an AI agent for the card game “Guandan.” Our goal was to create a platform that combined Guandan teaching with gameplay.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Used the DMC (Deep Monte Carlo) model for a foundation, and worked to incorporate additional rules in hopes that the AI agent would surpass human-level gameplay. However, the final model achieved a win rate of only 70%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Experimented with using MCTS (Monte Carlo Tree Search) to find the optimal strategy for the Jianzi game, but the method proved to be limited due to the large variety of card types and the high-dimensional action space.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contributions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Adjusted the penalty for playing a bomb at the beginning of the game: reduced the penalty for strong hands and increased it for weak hands.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Differentiated the penalty for straight flush (同花顺) and normal bombs, as their rankings differ significantly.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Added a function to play counter cards (压牌) to prevent the opponent from sneaking away too many single cards or sequences straight.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Noticed that the agent had an excessive tendency to play single cards, so I wrote a function to adjust this tendency.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;!--more--&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;video-demo&#34;&gt;Video Demo&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is our Demo &amp;ndash; Playing Guandan on terminal:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;video width=&#34;640&#34; height=&#34;380&#34; controls&gt;
  &lt;source src=&#34;http://localhost:1313/uploads/guandan.mov&#34; type=&#34;video/mp4&#34;&gt;
  Your browser does not support the video tag.
&lt;/video&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep Safety and Health Monitoring (ongoing, and highly likely that a paper will be published)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/project/bedside-safety-and-sleep-monitoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/project/bedside-safety-and-sleep-monitoring/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jun. 2024 - Present&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;Advisor:&lt;/strong&gt; Prof. Rong Zheng (Computing and Software, McMaster University)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Some wearable devices can monitor sleep quality. We aim to replace wearable devices with radar and machine learning methods
for sleep quality monitoring. This involves using radar to measure key data from the human body, building a model that takes radar data as input, and outputting sleep stages to reflect the user&amp;rsquo;s sleep status.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Contribute to process heart rate, respiration, and acceleration data, extract features as inputs for a decision tree, and design a rule-based decision tree capable of distinguishing sleep stages.In specific, We aim to use features related to heart rate (HR), respiration rate (RR), and acceleration (ACC) as inputs to predict three sleep stages (Wake, REM, NREM). My responsibility is to address scenarios with missing data. For example, how to determine sleep stages if only HR and RR are available, but ACC is missing.&lt;br&gt;
From online datasets, I found one dataset containing HR, RR, and sleep stage (denoted as D1) and another with HR, ACC, and sleep stage (denoted as D2). Initially, I attempted using Random Forest ensemble learning, training separate decision trees on each dataset and combining their results. However, the final accuracy barely approached but still fell short of 70%, showing poor performance.&lt;br&gt;
Later, I referred to the article titled &lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#&#34;&gt;Development and validation of an algorithm for the study of sleep using a biometric shirt in young healthy adults&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt; and adapted its rule-based decision tree approach. After modifications, the final prediction accuracy improved to 75%.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/uploads/Bedside_Safety_and_Sleep_Monitoring_presentation.pptx&#34;&gt;More details in this PPT&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
